jedec.org 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | JEDEC

### JEDEC’s Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. This notice summarizes our online information practices and outlines the choices you can make about your information. Links to this policy appear throughout the website, in the footer and on webforms where personal information is collected.

### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all personal information collected or submitted on the JEDEC website, including when ordering JEDEC products, registering to download published JEDEC standards and documents, registering to become a JEDEC member, registering to attend a JEDEC event, or contacting JEDEC for assistance. JEDEC collects the minimum amount of personal information necessary to fulfill these requests and the type of information collected varies depending on the request.

### The Way We Use Information

JEDEC uses the personal information that you provide to us for our internal purposes such as responding to your requests for information, contacting you, conducting internal analyses, and processing and completing orders and event registrations.

JEDEC uses PayPal or Authorize.net to process credit card transactions, and never has access to credit card information itself.

JEDEC uses domain cookies to identify single sessions which are deleted when you close your browser or the cookie expires. These cookies are not stored permanently and allow JEDEC to recognize registered users and permit access to downloadable material on the website.

JEDEC uses Google Analytics to understand how the website is used. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.

Website users who register to download documents and standards (“registrants”) have the opportunity to opt-in to the JEDEC email list. Registrants who opt-in will receive promotional and marketing communications from us and our partners. Any partners with whom JEDEC shares the information of our opt-in registrants are contractually bound to use this information only to perform the services we have contracted with them to provide.

For new member registrations, JEDEC uses the contact information provided for each company representative to contact you on an ongoing basis with information about your assigned committees, subcommittees and task groups. JEDEC also contacts members with promotional and marketing communications from us and our partners. Any partners with whom JEDEC shares member information are contractually bound to use this information only to perform the services we have contracted with them to provide.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How You Can Access or Correct Your Information

Users who have registered to download JEDEC standards and documents may login to the website and visit "My Account" to review, manage or delete their own personal profile. Users experiencing difficulty should contact [Arnaud Lebegue](mailto:arnaudl@jedec.org) or [Emily Desjardins](mailto:emilyd@jedec.org).

JEDEC members may login to the protected members’ website to manage their profile. JEDEC members may also contact [Arlene Collier](mailto:arlenec@jedec.org) for assistance with profile management and removal.

Individuals who have purchased JEDEC products or registered for a JEDEC event may contact [Emily Desjardins](mailto:emilyd@jedec.org) for assistance with deleting their information.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact the JEDEC IT Director, [Arnaud Lebegue](mailto:emilyd@jedec.org).
